

Sutrishna Anjoy

Site Reliability Engineer

• Profiles •

in <u>sutrisna-anjoy</u> LinkedIn

sutrisnaanjoy19 GitHub

o Skills o

Orchestration

Advanced

Kubernetes, Kustomize, Helm, ArgoCD, Docker

CI/CD

Advanced

Jenkins, GitLab, AR, Spinnaker

Monitoring & Alerting

Intermediate

Prometheus, Grafana, Alertmanager, Pagerduty, ELK

Others

Git, VSCode, Terraform, Google Cloud, AWS, Python, Groovy, C++, Bash, Linux, Networking, OS

• Awards •

MTech Topper

IIEST

Dec 2022

• Publications •

Lung Cancer detection using 2D CNN

Springer

Jun 2022

In this paper, we use 2D convolutional neural networks to detect malignant nodules from CT scan images. We use modified *VGG16* for the identification of lung cancer.

Springer URL

Summary

Site Reliability Engineer with 2 years of experience expertly managing and optimizing **Kubernetes** clusters on **Google Cloud**. Dedicated to ensuring high availability, scalability, and performance, with a knack for crafting efficient **Jenkins** pipelines to streamline deployment processes.

Experience

Media.net

Site Reliability Engineer

Mumbai, IN

Jul 2022 to Present

- Monitoring and maintaining multiple GKE clusters across regions.
- Analysis and planning of reducing cost of existing cloud resources used in the projects.
- Setting Logstash pipelines, Kibana alerts, watchers for Developers.
- Writing Jenkins pipelines to automate some of our repeating tasks.
- Used technologies like Kubernetes, Kustomize, Helm, Google Cloud
 (GKE, AR), ArgoCD & Rollouts, ELK, Jenkins, Docker, Git.

Media.net

SRE-Intern

Mumbai, IN

Feb 2022 - Jun 2022

- Understanding Linux, Networking, Distributed systems, Virtualization.
- Learning and practicing SRE concepts like Monitoring, CI/CD, containerization, orchestration.
- Reviewing and helping out in maintenance of GKE, ELK clusters.

Education

IIEST Shibpur

Computer Science and Engineering 9.63 CGPA

Masters in Technology

Sep 2020 - Jun 2022

- Area of study: Deeplearning.
- Wrote thesis on Identification of Lung Cancer Nodules from CT images using 2D Convolutional Neural Networks.
- https://www.iiests.ac.in/